1. callTestCase(findTestCase("OCS - DESKTOP/CALL- Age gate"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl("https://ocs.ca/?fts=0&preview_theme_id=74380642124")
9. maximizeWindow()
13. refresh()
17. delay(2)
21. executeJavaScript("var previewBar = document.getElementById("preview-bar-iframe"); previewBar.style.display = "none";", [])
25. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Date"), "12", true)
29. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/month"), "6", true)
33. delay(2)
37. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Year Dropdown"), "1990", true)
41. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/button_Verify"))
45. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Checkbox_CONFIRM AND ACKNOWLEDGE"))
49. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/button_CONFIRM"))
53. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/button_Start Browsing"))
57. delay(2)
61. refresh()
5. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
9. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"))
13. delay(2)
17. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/How cannabis works"))
21. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
25. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"))
29. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
33. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/The Effects of Cannabis"))
37. verifyTextPresent("The Effects of Cannabis", true)
41. delay(2)
45. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
49. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
53. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Endocannabinoids chevron"))
57. verifyTextPresent("The Endocannabinoid System", true)
61. delay(2)
65. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
69. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
73. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Read More -1"))
77. verifyTextPresent("The human reaction to cannabis.", false)
81. delay(2)
85. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
89. delay(2)
93. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Cannabis anatomy"))
97. delay(2)
101. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
105. delay(2)
109. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/CBD"))
113. delay(2)
117. verifyTextPresent("CANNABIS ANATOMY", false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
121. delay(2)
125. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
129. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
133. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Terpenes"))
137. click(findTestObject("Learn_spy/Page_Ontario Cannabis Store  Ontari/h3_Learn"))
141. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Learn_OR/Page_The Effects of Cannabis  Ontar/a_Read More"))
145. verifyTextPresent("Terpenes give cannabis strains their unique aromas.", true)
149. click(findTestObject("Learn_spy/Page_Ontario Cannabis Store  Ontari/h3_Learn"))
153. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Learn_OR/Page_How Cannabis Works  Ontario Ca/span_Cannabis Anatomy"))
157. click(findTestObject("Learn_spy/Page_Ontario Cannabis Store  Ontari/h3_Learn"))
161. verifyTextPresent("Terpenes give cannabis strains their unique aromas.", true)
165. delay(2)
169. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
173. delay(1)
177. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/THC"))
181. verifyTextPresent("THC is the component in cannabis that is primarily responsible for its intoxicating, psychoactive effects.", true)
185. delay(2)
189. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
193. delay(1)
197. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Read More -2"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
201. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
205. verifyTextPresent("The components of a complex plant.", true)
209. delay(2)
213. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
217. delay(2)
221. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Cannabis Consumption"))
225. delay(1)
229. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
233. delay(1)
237. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Cooking with cannabis"))
241. verifyTextPresent("Cannabis-infused foods are becoming more common, and careful preparation is required to avoid overconsumption.", true)
245. delay(2)
249. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
253. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
257. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/storing cannabis - chevron"))
261. verifyTextPresent("How to keep your family safe and your cannabis from spoiling.", true)
265. delay(2)
269. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
273. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
277. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Growing cannabis - chevron"))
281. verifyTextPresent("It is legal in Ontario to own and grow up to 4 cannabis plants in your own residential dwelling. Get beginner growing tips here.", true)
285. delay(2)
289. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
293. delay(2)
297. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Read More -3"))
301. delay(2)
305. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
309. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
313. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/How to Choose Cannabis Products"))
317. delay(1)
321. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
325. delay(1)
329. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Reading a product label - chevron"))
333. delay(2)
337. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
341. delay(1)
345. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/cannabinoid content - chveron"))
349. verifyTextPresent("Understanding Cannabinoid Content on Product Labels", true)
353. delay(2)
357. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
361. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
365. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Factors in Choosing Canna - chevron"))
369. verifyTextPresent("Factors in Choosing Cannabis Products", true)
373. delay(2)
377. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
381. delay(2)
385. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Read More -4"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
389. delay(2)
393. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
397. delay(2)
401. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Buying Cannabis at OCS plus accordian"))
405. delay(1)
409. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
413. delay(1)
417. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Why Legal Cannabis Costs more - chevron"))
421. verifyTextPresent("Four Reasons Why Legal Cannabis Costs More", true)
425. delay(2)
429. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
433. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Buying Cannabis at OCS plus accordian"))
437. delay(1)
441. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
445. delay(1)
449. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/why trust us - chevron"))
453. verifyTextPresent("Legal products and reliable information.", true)
457. delay(2)
461. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
465. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
469. delay(1)
473. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/about buying cannabis - chveron"))
477. delay(2)
481. verifyTextPresent("These facts are good to know before making a cannabis purchase.", true)
485. delay(2)
489. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
493. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
497. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Read More -5"))
501. delay(1)
505. verifyTextPresent("Buying Cannabis at OCS", true)
509. delay(2)
513. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
517. delay(2)
521. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Whats Legal plus accordian"))
525. delay(1)
529. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
533. delay(1)
537. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/History -part 1 - chveron"))
541. verifyTextPresent("A Brief History of Cannabis - Part 1", true)
545. delay(2)
549. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
553. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
557. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/History -part 2 - chveron"))
561. verifyTextPresent("A Brief History of Cannabis - Part 2", true)
565. delay(2)
569. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
573. delay(1)
577. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Legal Use of Cannabis in ontario - chevron"))
581. verifyTextPresent("What you need to know before your start shopping.", true)
585. delay(2)
589. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
593. delay(2)
597. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Read More -6"))
601. verifyTextPresent("Learn about cannabis laws.", true)
605. delay(2)
609. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
613. delay(2)
617. click(findTestObject("OCS-MOBILE /LEARN page/see the learn section button"))
621. verifyTextPresent("Learn about cannabis laws.", true)
625. delay(2)
629. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
633. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/a brief history of cannabis"))
637. verifyTextPresent("How to Grow Cannabis Outdoors", true)