1. callTestCase(findTestCase("OCS - DESKTOP/CALL- Age gate"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl("https://ocs.ca/?fts=0&preview_theme_id=74380642124")
9. maximizeWindow()
13. refresh()
17. delay(2)
21. executeJavaScript("var previewBar = document.getElementById("preview-bar-iframe"); previewBar.style.display = "none";", [])
25. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Date"), "12", true)
29. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/month"), "6", true)
33. delay(2)
37. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Year Dropdown"), "1990", true)
41. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/button_Verify"))
45. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Checkbox_CONFIRM AND ACKNOWLEDGE"))
49. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/button_CONFIRM"))
53. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/button_Start Browsing"))
57. delay(2)
61. refresh()
5. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
9. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
13. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
17. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/All accessories"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
21. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
25. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
29. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
33. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/Vaporizers"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
37. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
41. a = getWindowTitle(CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
45. comment(a)
49. b = "Vaporizers | Ontario Cannabis Store"
53. comment(b)
57. if (a == b)
2. comment("Some random page ")
61. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
65. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
69. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
73. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
77. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/Bongs - water pipes"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
81. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
85. a1 = getWindowTitle(CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
89. comment(a1)
93. b1 = "Bongs & Water Pipes | Ontario Cannabis Store"
97. comment(b1)
101. if (a1 == b1)
1. comment("correct window page ")
105. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
109. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
113. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
117. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
121. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/Handheld pipes"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
125. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
129. a11 = getWindowTitle(CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
133. comment(a11)
137. b11 = "Handheld Pipes | Ontario Cannabis Store"
141. comment(b11)
145. if (a11 == b11)
1. comment("correct window page ")
149. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
153. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
157. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
161. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
165. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/Papers -filters"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
169. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
173. a111 = getWindowTitle(CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
177. comment(a111)
181. b111 = "Papers & Filters | Ontario Cannabis Store"
185. comment(b111)
189. if (a111 == b111)
1. comment("correct window page ")
193. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
197. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
201. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
205. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
209. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/Grinders"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
213. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
217. a1111 = getWindowTitle(CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
221. comment(a1111)
225. b1111 = "Grinders | Ontario Cannabis Store"
229. comment(b1111)
233. if (a1111 == b1111)
1. comment("correct window page ")
237. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
241. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
245. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
249. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
253. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/Tools -kits"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
257. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
261. a11111 = getWindowTitle(CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
265. comment(a11111)
269. b11111 = "Multi-Tools & Kits | Ontario Cannabis Store"
273. comment(b11111)
277. if (a11111 == b11111)
1. comment("correct window page ")
281. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
285. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
289. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
293. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
297. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/Cleaning supplies"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
301. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
305. a12 = getWindowTitle(CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
309. comment(a12)
313. b12 = "Cleaning Supplies | Ontario Cannabis Store"
317. comment(b12)
321. if (a12 == b12)
1. comment("correct window page ")
325. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
329. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
333. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
337. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
341. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/Storage"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
345. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
349. a13 = getWindowTitle(CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
353. comment(a13)
357. b13 = "Storage | Ontario Cannabis Store"
361. comment(b)
365. if (a13 == b13)
1. comment("correct window page ")
369. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
373. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
377. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
381. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
385. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/Trays"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
389. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
393. a14 = getWindowTitle(CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
397. comment(a14)
401. b14 = "Trays | Ontario Cannabis Store"
405. comment(b14)
409. if (a14 == b14)
1. comment("correct window page ")
413. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
417. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
421. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
425. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
429. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/Infusers"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
433. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
437. a15 = getWindowTitle(CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
441. comment(a15)
445. b15 = "Infusers | Ontario Cannabis Store"
449. comment(b15)
453. if (a15 == b15)
1. comment("correct window page ")
457. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
461. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
465. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
469. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
473. executeJavaScript("var previewBar = document.getElementById("preview-bar-iframe"); previewBar.style.display = "none";", [])
477. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
481. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/Best selling pipes"))
485. delay(1, OPTIONAL)
489. flag = verifyTextPresent("Page Not Found", false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
493. comment("flag=" + flag)
497. if (flag == true)
501. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
505. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
509. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
513. executeJavaScript("var previewBar = document.getElementById("preview-bar-iframe"); previewBar.style.display = "none";", [])
517. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/Travel storage"))
521. flag1 = verifyTextPresent("Page Not Found", false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
525. comment("flag1=" + flag1)
529. if (flag1 == true)
533. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
537. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/ACCESSORIES menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
541. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
545. delay(1, OPTIONAL)
549. executeJavaScript("var previewBar = document.getElementById("preview-bar-iframe"); previewBar.style.display = "none";", [])
553. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
557. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Accessories page/Shop all acessories"))