1. callTestCase(findTestCase("OCS - DESKTOP/CALL- Age gate"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl("https://ocs.ca/?fts=0&preview_theme_id=74210314060")
9. maximizeWindow()
13. delay(2)
17. executeJavaScript("var previewBar = document.getElementById("preview-bar-iframe"); previewBar.style.display = "none";", [])
21. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Date"), "12", true)
25. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/month"), "6", true)
29. delay(2)
33. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Year Dropdown"), "1990", true)
37. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/button_Verify"))
41. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Checkbox_CONFIRM AND ACKNOWLEDGE"))
45. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/button_CONFIRM"))
49. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/button_Start Browsing"))
53. delay(2)
57. refresh()
5. delay(2)
9. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
13. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
17. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
21. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Dried flower"))
25. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
29. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"))
33. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
37. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
41. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Dried flower - Indica dominant"))
45. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
49. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
53. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
57. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Dried flower - sativa dominant"))
61. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
65. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
69. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
73. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
77. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Dried flower - Hybrid"))
81. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
85. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
89. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
93. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
97. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Shop all dried flower"))
101. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
105. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
109. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
113. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
117. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Prerolled - Plus accordian"))
121. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
125. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
129. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
133. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
137. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Prerolled - Indica dominant"))
141. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
145. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
149. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
153. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
157. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
161. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Prerolled - sativa dominant"))
165. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
169. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
173. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
177. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
181. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
185. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Prerolled - Hybrid"))
189. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
193. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
197. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
201. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
205. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
209. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Shop all prerolled"))
213. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
217. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
221. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
225. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
229. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
233. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Oils - plus accordian"))
237. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
241. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
245. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
249. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
253. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Oils - Bottled oils"))
257. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
261. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
265. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
269. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
273. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
277. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Oils - oral sprays"))
281. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
285. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
289. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
293. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
297. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
301. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/shop all oils"))
305. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
309. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
313. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
317. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
321. click(findTestObject("MOBILE OBJECTS/Capsules chevron"))
325. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
329. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
333. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
337. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
341. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Shop by plant type - plus accordian"))
345. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
349. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
353. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
357. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Shop by plant type - Indica dominant"))
361. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
365. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
369. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
373. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
377. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
381. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Shop by plant type - sativa dominant"))
385. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
389. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
393. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
397. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
401. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
405. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Shop by plant type - Hybrid"))
409. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
413. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
417. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
421. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
425. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Collections - plus accordian"))
429. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
433. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/CANNABIS menu - English"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
437. delay(1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
441. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Cannabis page/Collections- New products"))