1. callTestCase(findTestCase("OCS - DESKTOP/CALL- Age gate"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl("https://ocs.ca/?fts=0&preview_theme_id=74380642124")
9. maximizeWindow()
13. refresh()
17. delay(2)
21. executeJavaScript("var previewBar = document.getElementById("preview-bar-iframe"); previewBar.style.display = "none";", [])
25. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Date"), "12", true)
29. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/month"), "6", true)
33. delay(2)
37. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Year Dropdown"), "1990", true)
41. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/button_Verify"))
45. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Checkbox_CONFIRM AND ACKNOWLEDGE"))
49. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/button_CONFIRM"))
53. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/button_Start Browsing"))
57. delay(2)
61. refresh()
5. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
9. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"))
13. delay(2)
17. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/How cannabis works"))
21. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
25. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"))
29. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
33. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/The Effects of Cannabis"))
37. verifyTextPresent("The Effects of Cannabis", true)
41. delay(2)
45. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
49. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
53. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Endocannabinoids chevron"))
57. verifyTextPresent("The Endocannabinoid System", true)
61. delay(2)
65. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
69. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
73. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Read More -1"))
77. verifyTextPresent("The human reaction to cannabis.", false)
81. delay(2)
85. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
89. delay(2)
93. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Cannabis anatomy"))
97. delay(2)
101. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
105. delay(2)
109. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/CBD"))
113. delay(2)
117. verifyTextPresent("CANNABIS ANATOMY", false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
121. delay(2)
125. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/Age gate and Mega menu/Header/LEARN menu - En"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
129. delay(2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
133. click(findTestObject("OCS-DESKTOP/LEARN page/Terpenes"))
137. click(findTestObject("Learn_spy/Page_Ontario Cannabis Store  Ontari/h3_Learn"))
141. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Learn_OR/Page_The Effects of Cannabis  Ontar/a_Read More"))
145. verifyTextPresent("Terpenes give cannabis strains their unique aromas.", true)